SUBJECT: ANNUAL IN-SERVICE RECORD FORM        REFERENCE #8080
                                              PAGE: 1 
                                                OF: 1
            Delivering Home Health Solutions
       Neighborhood Home Health Services, Inc.EFFECTIVE: 06/01/10
APPROVED BY: GOVERNING BODY                   REVISED: 08/01/2020

  I HAVE RECEIVED AND ACKNOWLEDGE ALL STANDARDS OF CARE 

  FOR THE MANDATORY ANNUAL IN-SERVICES EDUCATION AND 

  TRAININGS ON:

   CI MANUAL

   ❑ ALZHEIMERS EDUCATION HANDOUT

   C:1 PATIENT RIGHTS HANDOUT

   CI TUBERCULOSIS EDUCATION & COMPETENCY EXAM

   CI SAFE MEDICAL DEVICE ACT EDUCATION

   CI SAFETY & SECURITY EDUCATION

   CI EXPOSURE & INFECTION CONTROL EDUCATION & COMPETENCY
     EXAM

   L3 COVID- 1 9

   CI ABUSE, NEGLET, AND EXPLOITATION EXAM

   U REPORTING INCIDENTS EDUCATION & COMPETENCY EXAM

   ❑BODY MECHANICS & PATIENT TRANSFERS

   LI DISASTER PREPAREDNESS EDUCATION


   CONTRACTOR NAME(NOMBRE):
   CONTRACTOR SIGNATURE (FIRMA): 

   DATE (FECHA):




   NHHS                                  ANNUAL TRAINING RECORD FORM

