                _        Dvisnig ilea Muth Salve,
 NEIGHBORHOOD HOME HEALTH SERVICES. INC. 
                "IN-SERVICE" EXAM 
        ABUSE. NEGLECT. AND EXPLOITATION

7. Is it a Florida Statutes, to penalize a person who has committed abuse, neglect, or exploitation 
 punishable by misdemeanor of the second degree?
 a) Yes
 b) No


8. High risk circumstances for abuse, neglect, and exploitation include:
 a) Vulnerable adult is becoming weak and dependent.
 b) There is a family history of abuse.
 c) There is a desire for the person's inheritance.
 d) All of the above.

9. Indicators of abuse, neglect, and exploitation include:
 a) Unexplained bruises
 b) Unexplained fractures
 c) Unexplained burns
 d) All of the above

 10. Behavior Indicators include:
 a) Assaults others
 b) Threatens self-harm or suicide
 c) Recent or sudden changes in behavior or attitudes
 d) All of the above

