                        Ddnvim thew Hut* Sablatt
 NEIGHBORHOOD HOME HEALTH SERVICES. INC. 
               "IN-SERVICE" EXAM 
        ABUSE. NEGLECT. AND EXPLOITATION


                       NAME.



1. What Is the definition of neglect?
 a) Failure or omission on part of the caregiver or vulnerable adult to provide the care, supervision, 
   and services necessary to maintain the physical and mental health of a vulnerable adult.
 b) Being able at provide care to a vulnerable adult.
 c) Calling a doctor to report a patient's status.


 2. What Is the definition of sexual abuse?
 a) Having intimate relations with spouse.
 b) Acts of sexual nature committed in the presence of a vulnerable adult without that person's 
   informed consent.
 c) Taking a friend out for Ice cream.

 3. What is the definition of a vulnerable adult?
 a) A 16 year old who can drive.
 b) A 21 year who graduated from college
 c) A person 18 years of age or older, whose ability to perform the normal ADts, or provide for his 
   own care/protection is impaired.

 4. Definition of exploitation:
 a) A person, who stands in a position of trust and confidence with a vulnerable adult knowingly, by 
   deception or Intimidation, benefits of someone other than the vulnerable adult.
 b) A person who ships thing out of the country.
 c) Fireworks on the 4th of July.


 S. True or False?
   It is mandatory to report abuse, neglect, and/or exploitation.
 a) True
 b) False


 6. What are the barriers to identification of abuse and neglect?
 a) Victim refuses to acknowledge the problem.
 b) Victim feels too embarrassed or guilty.
 c) Victim is unaware of other options.
 d) All of the above.

